{
    "id": "78df9ae1dcb44f22953ac8fb9ad633e9",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise (Vocabulary)",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I am tired of ..................... to your demands.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "satisfying",
                "pandering",
                "falling",
                "meeting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "edfe83b4a74c4bccb167bc33b7b016b0"
        },
        {
            "question": "In order to be successful, businesses have to …………………. to the needs of their customers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cater",
                "master",
                "please",
                "assimilate"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "df11d870cafc49f29a2baa8ceb8ae6bf"
        },
        {
            "question": "They tried to reassure me but I was still not able to ………………… my fears.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "prevent",
                "annul",
                "reduce",
                "curtail"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a0dc49c7a47a4ee7beb1cac32d4f836a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I always preferred the …………………. of the big city.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "obscurity",
                "anonymity",
                "privileges"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ec93412254894b199b48e65445d53f7e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The General ...................... the defeat to a series of tactical errors.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "blamed",
                "pointed",
                "ascribed",
                "accredited"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "795a0269fdfc42e687831f97a0e89715"
        },
        {
            "question": "They cast ………………….. on his integrity.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "slanders",
                "aspersions",
                "remarks",
                "skepticism"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f818ca2f1e514fe0b53509fb25e3d481"
        },
        {
            "question": "A mugger ..................... him on the dark street.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "assailed",
                "ascribed",
                "hailed",
                "treated"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e73beb78521e4a94a75f721ef54e10e9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Most people ………………….. to my views on the matter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "accept",
                "approve",
                "admit",
                "assent"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "21d9559ddda74b75a9d01fdfd558735c"
        },
        {
            "question": "My constant reassurance could not ..................... their fears.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "assuage",
                "avoid",
                "soothe",
                "prevent"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7cdb4dcf611643bf92472cb2f217fa49"
        },
        {
            "question": "Our plans have gone .........................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wrecked",
                "awry",
                "crooked",
                "shattered"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2874428d823c4b5c9864ac93f934725f"
        }
    ]
}